# SIVALAL SADASIVAN

# Office Administrator

+966 540804958, +91 9847666887 \* https://www.linkedin.com/in/sivalal-sadasivan/\* sivan37@yahoo.com

#### **PROFILE**

Experienced Administrator with a demonstrated history of working in the education management industry seeks to join your growing organization as an Executive Office Administrator, Skilled in Management, Supervisory skills and Training. Competent in prioritizing, organizing and working with little supervision, ensuring things run smoothly behind the scenes of a busy office.

### CORE COMPETENCIES

- Tolerant and flexible
- ❖ Interactive communication skills
- Cash register familiarity
- Friendly demeanor
- Outstanding interpersonal skills
- Training and development

- Office administration
- Staff management
- Technological instruction [SMART Board aptitude]
- ❖ Travel arrangements *etc*.

### PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

ZAMIL TRAINING CENTER (ZHIIT- SAUDI ARABIA)
Administrative Secretary cum Department Supervisor/ December 2012 – Present

- Computerized office activities, maintained customer communications.
- Handled cash register & financial reporting.
- \* Responded to customer questions and requests in a sincere and friendly manner.
- \* Completed all daily tasks and special assignments with an efficient and quality-driven approach.
- ❖ Assisted customers with prompt and polite support in-person and via telephone.
- \* Handled all customer relations issues in a gracious manner and in accordance with company policies

# MOE - REPUBLIC OF MALDIVES ESL Trainer, January 2008 – DECEMBER 2012

- ❖ Worked with other teachers and administrators to evaluate and revise school programs.
- Created lesson plans and scheduled each day to promote maximum student learning and enrichment.
- Prepared quizzes, tests and examinations to gauge how well students were learning.
- \* Cooperated with parents to support students' learning and healthy development in school and at home

# A.E.S Central School, Malappuram- Kerala India ESL Teacher June 2006- December 2007

#### **EDUCATION**

## KERAL STATE UNIVERSITY, KERALA STATE, INDIA Bachelor of Art in English, May 1992

# SARVODAYA VIDYALAYA TRIVANDRUM, KERALA, INDIA Grade X (ICSE) March 1986

### ADDITIONAL SKILLS

- Proficient in Microsoft Office
- Bilingual Malayalam and English
- Audio-visual aid implementation
- TESOL & IELTS Certification [2010]

- Group and individual instruction
- Classroom discipline
- Kind and empathetic educator

## REFERENCES

✓ Mr. Mohammed Naseer

Deputy Principal, Shaviyani A.E.C.

Republic of Maldives

Mob: 0096 09664151/ Phone: +960 6540062

MOE, Republic of Maldives

✓ Dr. Mohammed Abdullah Sharif

Training Director ZHIIT (<a href="http://www.zamil-training.com">http://www.zamil-training.com</a>)

MOB: +966 0557200795(KSA) / +973 39417009 (BAHRAIN)

